export const intPrepTime = [{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The train left _________ time, right at 6pm.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "We were just _________ time for everyone to sing happy birthday.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "_________ the end of the day, we all need love.",
        "options": [
            "At",
            "In",
            "On"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "We wound up painting the house gray _________ the end.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "He finished the marathon _________ just over 3.5 hours.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Many of the cathedrals in Europe were built _________ the Middle Ages.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "He can whistle and speak _________ the same time.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "He wasn't _________ time for work for the 3rd time in a week and was let go.",
        "options": [
            "at",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "_________ first, we didn't really get on but now we're great friends.",
        "options": [
            "At",
            "In",
            "On"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "_________ the end of the concert, the artist sang their most popular song.",
        "options": [
            "At",
            "In",
            "On"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    }
]